{
  "minecraft-version": "Minecraft version",
  "java-version": "Java version",
  "fabric-version": "Fabric loader version",
  "quilt-version": "Quilt loader version",
  "plugin-load-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be loaded.",
  "pocketmine-version": "Pocketmine version",
  "bedrock-version": "Bedrock version",
  "forge-version": "Forge version",
  "neoforge-version": "NeoForge version",
  "magma-version": "Magma version",
  "mohist-version": "Mohist version",
  "arclight-version": "Arclight version",
  "custom-skin-loader-version": "CustomSkinLoader version",
  "authme-shutdown-problem": "The plugin 'AuthMe' fails to load and shuts the server down.",
  "pex-config-problem": "The configuration of the plugin 'PermissionsEx' is invalid.",
  "ambiguous-plugin-name-problem": "There are multiple plugin files for the plugin name '{{plugin-name}}': '{{first-plugin-path}}' and '{{second-plugin-path}}'.",
  "plugin-dependency-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is missing the required plugin '{{dependency-plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-dependencies-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is missing the required plugins {{dependency-plugin-names}}.",
  "plugin-disabling-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be disabled.",
  "plugin-enabling-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' could not be enabled.",
  "plugin-runtime-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' has a problem while running.",
  "forge-confirm-problem": "Forge requires your confirmation to apply changes and start the server.",
  "mod-dependency-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is missing the required mod {{dependency-mod-name}}.",
  "mod-dependency-problem-plural": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is missing the required mods {{dependency-mod-list}}.",
  "mod-duplicate-problem": "There are multiple mod files for the mod name '{{mod-name}}': '{{first-mod-path}}' and '{{second-mod-path}}'.",
  "mod-duplicate-problem-no-path": "There are multiple mod files for the mod name '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-exception-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has thrown an exception.",
  "mod-fatal-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' has a fatal error.",
  "world-missing-mod-problem": "The world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' which appears to be missing.",
  "world-mod-version-problem": "This world was saved with mod '{{mod-name}}' version {{mod-expected-version}} and it is now at version {{mod-current-version}}.",
  "plugin-incompatible-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' is incompatible with your current server version.",
  "aquatic-world-on-older-version-problem": "The current world was created/loaded with Minecraft 1.13 or higher. The new format cannot be loaded in any older version.",
  "old-player-directory-problem": "The server has detected an old player directory in the world save.",
  "command-run-solution": "Run the command '{{command}}'.",
  "authme-shutdown-solution": "Set 'stopServer' to 'true'.",
  "configure-plugin": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}}.",
  "configure-plugin-with-file": "Configure the plugin {{plugin-name}} ({{suggested-file}}).",
  "plugin-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-install-solution": "Install the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "plugin-remove-solution": "Remove the plugin '{{plugin-name}}'.",
  "file-delete-solution": "Delete the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "file-edit-solution": "Edit the file '{{file-path}}'.",
  "mod-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different version of the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "mod-install-solution-with-version": "Install the mod '{{mod-name}}' with version {{mod-version}}.",
  "mod-remove-solution": "Remove the mod '{{mod-name}}'.",
  "aquatic-version-install-solution": "Update the server software to 1.13 or newer.",
  "plugin-command-exception-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' cannot execute the command '{{command}}'.",
  "ticking-block-entity-problem": "A block in the world is causing problems.",
  "remove-block-solution": "Remove the block from the world, e.g. with MCEdit.",
  "do-nothing-solution": "Do nothing. This problem might fix itself.",
  "chunk-load-exception-problem": "There was an exception while loading the world chunks.",
  "remove-chunk-solution": "Remove the problematic chunk from the world, e.g. with MCEdit or by removing the region file.",
  "multiverse-load-problem": "The world '{{world-name}}' could not be loaded because it contains errors and is probably corrupt.",
  "world-repair-solution": "Repair the world '{{world-name}}', e.g. by using Minecraft Region Fixer or MCEdit.",
  "world-duplicate-problem": "World '{{world-name}}' is a duplicate of another world and has been prevented from loading.",
  "mod-wrong-minecraft-version-problem": "The mod '{{mod-name}}' is not compatible with the Minecraft version {{minecraft-version}}.",
  "forge-install-different-version-solution": "Install a different Forge version.",
  "malformed-encoding-problem": "Something (probably the MOTD) contains malformed formatting codes.",
  "change-motd-solution": "Change the server MOTD.",
  "bedrock-authentication-whitelist-problem": "Using a whitelist without online authentication is not allowed.",
  "bedrock-authentication-allowlist-problem": "Using an allowlist without online authentication is not allowed.",
  "disable-whitelist-solution": "Disable the whitelist.",
  "disable-allowlist-solution": "Disable the allowlist.",
  "enable-authentication-solution": "Enable the online authentication.",
  "undefined-mod-dependency-problem": "A mod is missing the required mod {{dependency-mod-name}}.",
  "version-downgrade-problem": "Your world was used on a newer version before.",
  "version-downgrade-solution": "Install a newer version of Minecraft.",
  "generate-new-world-solution": "Generate a new world.",
  "bedrock-dbstorage-chain-problem": "Unable to decrypt world. Marketplace worlds can't be installed on dedicated servers.",
  "mod-incompatible-problem": "The mods '{{first-mod-name}}' and '{{second-mod-name}}' are incompatible.",
  "server-install-different-version-solution": "Install the version '{{software-version}}' of your server software.",
  "plugin-api-version-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' needs version '{{software-version}}' of your server software.",
  "plugin-java-version-problem": "The plugin '{{plugin-name}}' requires Java version {{java-version}} or later to run.",
  "change-java-version-solution": "Change your Java version to {{java-version}} or later.",
  "ticking-entity-problem": "The entity '{{name}}' at the location {{location}} is causing issues while ticking.",
  "remove-entity-solution": "Remove the entity '{{name}}' at the location {{location}}.",
  "plugin-regional-ticking-problem": "The plugin {{plugin-name}} does not support regional ticking.",
  "install-non-regional-ticking-software-solution": "Install a software without regional ticking, like {{software-name}}.",
  "type-client": "Client Log",
  "type-server": "Server Log",
  "type-proxy": "Proxy Log",
  "type-content": "Content Log",
  "type-crash-report": "Crash Report",
  "type-unknown": "Unknown Log",
  "forge-language-provider-version-problem": "The mod '{{mod-file}}' requires '{{required-version}}', but '{{found-version}}' is installed."
}
